{
    "subject": "resource/Cidade_Negra",
    "predicate": "property/origin",
    "object": "resource/Brazil",
    "human_readable": "Cidade Negra originated from Brazil.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8820576071739197,
            "question": "Where did Cidade Negra originate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7191029191017151,
            "question": "What country is Cidade Negra from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4928622543811798,
            "question": "What are some notable aspects of Cidade Negra's history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4023536145687103,
            "question": "How would you describe the people of Cidade Negra?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40221068263053894,
            "question": "What is the culture like in Cidade Negra?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35473108291625977,
            "question": "Is Cidade Negra a city, region, or something else?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30294397473335266,
            "question": "Are there any unique traditions or festivals celebrated in Cidade Negra?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22662417590618134,
            "question": "What is the climate like in Cidade Negra?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21781966090202332,
            "question": "Does Cidade Negra have any famous landmarks or attractions?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1636519730091095,
            "question": "What are some popular foods or dishes associated with Cidade Negra?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Cidade Negra originated from Brazil.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1138_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Cidade Negra have any famous landmarks or attractions?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1138_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the climate like in Cidade Negra?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1138_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any unique traditions or festivals celebrated in Cidade Negra?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1138_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1138_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1138_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1138_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1138_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1138_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1138_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1138_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1138_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1138_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1138_92.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Cidade Negra is a Brazilian reggae band formed in Rio de Janeiro, which supports the statement that Cidade Negra originated from Brazil."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}